<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>StarAi: Deep Reinforcement Learning Course on StarAi Deep Reinforcement Learning Course</title>
    <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/</link>
    <description>Recent content in StarAi: Deep Reinforcement Learning Course on StarAi Deep Reinforcement Learning Course</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://starai-course.github.io/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 0 : Introduction to Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture0/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description In this lecture, we will take you on a journey into the near future by discussing the recent developments in the field of Reinforcement Learning - by introducing you to what Reinforcement Learning is, how it differs from Deep Learning and the future impact of RL technology.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Additional Learning Material  Andrej Karpathy&amp;rsquo;s ConvNetJS Deep Q Learning Demo  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 1: Epsilon-Greedy &amp; the multiarmed bandit problem</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture1/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description In this lecture, we introduce you to your very first RL algorithm, Epsilon Greedy. We start off by exploring a toy problem known as the &amp;ldquo;multi armed bandit problem&amp;rdquo; or in english- how to win at slot machines! We then dive down into how Epsilon-Greedy solves the bandit problem, go on a detour introducing OpenAi Gym (and why it is important!) and finally hand you over to your first exercise, solving the bandit problem in OpenAi Gym.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 2: Markov Decision Processes, Dynamic Programming</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture2/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Disclaimer: This is the most mathematical lecture out of the StarAi series. Whilst we endeavoured to make the StarAi content as accessible as possible, this particular lecture covers the base fundamentals &amp;amp; therefore contains the most formulas. If formulas is not for you please proceed to week 3. If however you would like to dive deeper down the mathematical formulation of the RL framework stick around for lecture 2!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 3: Tabular Q Gridworld</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture3/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description In this session, participants will focus on a specific method of Temporal Difference Learning called Tabular Q Learning. Participants will learn the theory behind Q Learning, implement the different components bit by bit and combine these components to solve the robot in a maze scenario.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Lecture Slides StarAi Lecture 3 &amp;amp; 4 TabularQ slides
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Exercise Follow the link below to access the exercises for lecture 3:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 4:  Tabular Q Cartpole</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture4/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description In this session, participants will explore the problem of an environment where observations are continuous variables. Participants will learn the discretisation technique and implement this with the previous components to solve the problem of keeping a cart pole upright without having any understanding of the observations.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Lecture Slides StarAi Lecture 3 &amp;amp; 4 TabularQ slides
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Exercise Follow the link below to access the exercises for lecture 4:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 5:  NQL Theory</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture5/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Neural Q-Learning builds on the theory developed in previous sessions, augmenting the tabular Q-Learning algorithm with the powerful function approximation capabilities of Neural Networks. NQL is the &amp;ldquo;base&amp;rdquo; algorithm unifying Neural Networks and Reinforcement Learning, and participants will be exposed to both the impressive generalization properties of this algorithm, as well as some of it&amp;rsquo;s potential drawbacks and limitations.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Lecture Slides StarAi Lecture 5 part 1 Neural Q Theory slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 6:  DQN</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture6/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Deep Q-Networks refer to the method proposed by Deepmind in 2014 to learn to play ATARI2600 games from the raw pixel observations. This hugely influential method kick-started the resurgence in interest in Deep Reinforcement Learning, however it&amp;rsquo;s core contributions deal simply with the stabilization of the NQL algorithm. In these session these key innovations (Experience Replay, Target Networks, and Huber Loss) are stepped though, taking the participants from the relatively unstable NQL algorithm to a fully-implemented DQN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 7:  Policy Gradient Methods</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture7/</guid>
      <description>Video &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Please note: since last teaching the Policy Gradient content we have discovered two logical errors. Will be updating &amp;amp; reposting the content soon. Stay tuned.
In previous lectures, you were introduced to DQN - an algorithm that falls under the first major branch of Reinforcement Learning, &amp;ldquo;Value Based Methods&amp;rdquo;. In this lecture, we introduce you to &amp;ldquo;Policy Gradient methods&amp;rdquo; the second major branch of Reinforcement Learning where we learn to manipulate the object we care about the most - the policy - directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 8:  PySC2</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture8/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Starcraft 2 is a real time strategy game with highly complicated dynamics and rich multi-layered gameplay - which also makes it an ideal environment for AI research. PySC2 is Deepmind&amp;rsquo;s open source library for interfacing with Blizzard&amp;rsquo;s Starcraft 2 game. This session will introduce the PySC2 API, the observation space and the action spaces available &amp;amp; participants will build a simple Q learning agent to play the Move to Beacon minigame provided with PySC2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonus:  Rainbow</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture9/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Disclaimer: We feel that this lecture is not as polished as the rest of our content but decided to release it in the bonus section, under the hope that the community might find some value out of it. Enjoy!
The StarAi team is excited to offer a lecture &amp;amp; exercises on one of the the most cutting edge, end-to-end value based reinforcement learning algorithms out there - Deepmind&amp;rsquo;s rainbow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonus: the A2C algorithm</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture10/</guid>
      <description>Video  &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Description Disclaimer: We feel that this lecture is not as polished as the rest of our content but decided to release it in the bonus section, under the hope that the community might find some value out of it. Enjoy!
A2C is an algorithm &amp;ldquo;framework&amp;rdquo; that combines value &amp;amp; policy based methodologies discussed in previous lectures.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Lecture Slides StarAi Bonus Lecture 2 A2C slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonus: Additional Learning Material</title>
      <link>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://starai-course.github.io/course/lecture11/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Additional Learning Material &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Further Learnings - Foundations:
Intro to Reinforcement Learning by David Silver (Deepmind)
Reinforcement Learning: An Introduction (textbook)
Denny Britz Github Repo
OpenAi Spinning Up in Deep RL
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Further Learnings - Advanced:
Berkeley Deep RL Bootcamp
CS294 Deep Reinforcement Learning (Berkeley)
Deepmind&amp;rsquo;s IMPALA RL Framework
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>